Is Princess Peach and Waluigi the same person?
This question came to me when I realized that
most men are sexually attracted to...
...Waluigi
At first, it sounds ridiculous. But Nintendo has
a history of cross-dressing.
Sheik...
Link...
Fire Emblem:
Fire Emblem: All of them.
Also, his exclusion from Smash Ultimate is unthinkable.
Waluigi is not only the
most popular Nintendo character...
...but he's also the best character
according to several scientific studies.
Well, I think he IS in the game.
And, I can prove it.
Let's start by looking at his
backstory in the Nintendo canon.
What the fuck?
The manual from Mario Tennis did not mess around.
The name "Nectarin" also appears
in the Super Mario cereal/serial...
...and it refers to the Mushroom King.
YEAH, the Mushroom Kingdom has a king.
I bet you had forgotten Peach was a Princess.
That's why when she gets kidnapped,
they don't send Mushroom Special Ops.
They send a random fat Italian.
Ok, so they are siblings.
Princess Peach and Princess Waluigi.
No, they can't be.
Because in Mario Party 5, if you pick them as a team...
...you get the name "Anti-Couple)
Had they been siblings,
it would have said "Perfect Couple".
(oh no)
Because they are Royalty.
(oh ok)
It's what they do.
So they have the same father...
They look EXACTLY the same.
And in Mario Party 8, their team name is
"Sweet and Sour".
That's not 2 different things!
That's ONE sauce.
Ok, still a bit far-fetched.
Is this even psychologically possible?
Yeah!
Think about it.
You have a princess named after a fruit
that only tastes good for, like, 3 days.
And her boyfriend is a plumber.
That loves to murder cute animals.
Yet, she is happy, 24/7.
And that shows she is...
And that shows she is
severely depressed and miserable.
How can she escape this reality?
Throw her servants to Chain-Chomps.
Roman Emperor Style.
Instead, she created a miserable Italian.
To play tennis.
And then she grew 30 centimeters.
Waluigi is a beautiful princess, and the
reason he's not in Smash, is because...
...Peach gets to fufill her fantasies of beating up Mario.
She doesn't need him.
It's hard to say how long Nintendo have wanted a princess with Multiple Personality Disorder.
Since Mario Tennis?
Since Mario 64?
Since the 1800s?
If you play the original Mario, and you can tell this is not fake because I'm filming the screen.
In the last room...
Looks normal, correct?
But if I INVERT the colors...
IT'S...
Nothing happens.
I did something wrong.
But if I INVERT the colors...
...you will see a massive...
WAHHHHHHHHHH
Now, you are probably 100% convinced.
With ZERO questions.
But I'm going to leave you with the
biggest evidence of them all.
At E3 2008...
...a GameTrailers reporter asked Shigeru Miyamoto about Trumpets in Wii Music.
And Shigeru responded...
And that's...
And that's why I have a lot of pictures of just that.
And this video proves you aren't allowed
to judge my
*SLURP*
...collection.